Exit Art "Reactions" exhibit collection
Prints & Photographs Division, Library of Congress
Exit Art "Reactions" exhibit collection2001-2002
LOT 13520
Exit Art (Gallery: New York, N.Y.)
ca. 2,550 items 11 x 8.5 in.
Prints & Photographs Division Library of Congress Washington, D.C.
Exit Art, an alternative gallery space in New York City, mounted the exhibition "Reactions: A Global Response to the 9/11 Attacks," in January 2002. Recognizing that many people had an urgent need to freely communicate their feelings, the staff sent out a worldwide appeal by letter and e-mail for individuals to send in creative responses. With one simple criterion, that each work be sized 8 1/2 x 11 inches, 2,443 pieces went on view at the gallery.
For information about Prints and Photographs Division collections and services, see the Prints & Photographs Division's Reading Room Home Page.
Selected Search Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the Library's online catalog. They are grouped by name of person or organization, by subject or location, and by occupation and listed alphabetically therein.
Organizations
Exit Art (Gallery: New York, N.Y.); Exit Art (Gallery: New York, N.Y.)--Exhibitions & displays.
Subjects
September 11 Terrorist Attacks, 2001.
Form/Genre
Manuscripts--2000-2010.; Pictures--2000-2010.
Administrative Information
Provenance
Purchase; Exit Art Gallery; 2002; DLC/PP-2002:081
Additional form available
Digital scans for ca. 50 items along with their associated descriptions are available through the Prints & Photographs Online Catalog, by searching using the call number (or title), "[input call number or title]"
Biographical Note
The "Reactions" exhibition was conveived and organized by Exit Art/The First World, Inc., New York City as a means to document the personal reactions of people world wide following the terrorist attacks of September 11th. Over 2,500 submissions were received and exhibited at Exit Art's gallery.
Scope and Content Note
Pictures and manuscripts (collages, digital prints, drawings, paintings, photographs, poetry, letters, etc.) by professional artists, non-artists, and children reflecting personal responses to the terrorist attacks of September 11th, 2001.
Organization of the Papers
Organized by exhibition number.
http://lccn.loc.gov/2003653077
Container List
- Aaron
  - Not Alone, 0001; 1972; Photo of police on corner
- Abad, Sara
  - [Untitled], photographs; 0002; 1445; Three photos of WTC smoking from across river arranged horizontally
- Abecassis, David
  - [Untitled], 0003; 1857; Portrait
- Abelli, Jill
  - [Untitled], white sheet of paper; 0004; 2044
- Abend, Monica
  - [Untitled], digital image; 0005; 798
- Abramowitz, Irene Miller
  - Future Skyline as Seen from Ellis Island Ferry, 0006; 484; "Future skyline..."
- Abrams, Garnet
  - [Untitled], digital image; 0007; 2095; Angel's face with halo over it
- Abrams, John
  - [Untitled], 0008; 264; Blue "angles"
- Hardy, Laroyce Adames
  - [Untitled], 0009; 1691; Trees and school
- Adams, Marina
  - Strange Tongue, reproduction of original painting; 0010; 610; Try to hang side by side with #611
- Adels, Heather
  - [Untitled], drawing; 0011; 323; Rocks and hands
- Adey, Cesca
  - [Untitled], text on paper; 0012; 826; 2 stanza poem
- Adler, Julie
  - [Untitled], 0013; 1036; Bird in middle
- Adrienne, Karen
  - [Untitled], 0014; 1342; Squiggly lines
- Afiouni, Lila
  - Winter's Cry, aquatint etching; 0015; 1011; Stripped forms on right side with a black form at center-left
- Agard
  - [Untitled], 0016; 1172; Plant and column
- Aguilar, Jesus
  - [Untitled], 0018; 541; Breasts
- Aguilar, Margarita
  - [Untitled], 0019; 50; Letter via email
- Ahrens, June
  - [Untitled], 0020; 350; The Healing Heart Project 1 of 3
- Ahrens, June
  - [Untitled], 0021; 351; "Imagine perpetual light" 2 of 3
- Ahrens, June
  - [Untitled], 0022; 352; Healing Heart with safety pins 3 of 3
- Aimi, Andrea R
  - Twins, ink on paper; 0023; 903
- Alatriste, William
  - Californian Actor with His VW Peace Bus, Chelsea Piers NYC, c-print; 0025; 2058; Guy w/cowboy hat
- Alatriste, William
  - Babakan, 6th Avenue Flag-seller, c-print; 0026; 2054; Guy w/flags
- Alatriste, William
  - National Guardsmen in Makeshift Booth, Chinatown, NYC, c-print; 0027; 2055
- Alatriste, William
  - Jewish War Veteran, 5th Avenue, Veteran's Day Parade, c-print; 0028; 2057
- Alatriste, William
  - Mooky, Israeli Tow-truck Operator, 7th Avenue and Grove St., NYC, c-print; 0029; 2056
- Alava Crisostomo, Gema
  - Bolas, 0030; 2017; Graph paper w/balls
- Albanese, L.
  - [Untitled], paper collage; 0031; 446
- Albritton, Doree
  - Requiem, mixed media; 0032; 1029
- Aldan, Rachel
  - [Untitled], 0033; 213; Part of group from students of the Hudson School, "Losing something big has brought America closer together"
- Aldridge, Simon
  - [Untitled], paint on mylar; 0033b; 3252
- Aldrete, Anajose
  - [Untitled], 0034; 3041
- Alexander, Stuart
  - The Portal Cap, 0037; 1914; Elevation
- Alexander, Stuart
  - The Portal Cap, 0038; 1911
- Alexander, Stuart
  - The Portal Cap, 0039; 1910
- Alexis, Michel
  - [Untitled], 0040; 447; Propeller on white pages
- Ali, Kazim
  - [Untitled], xerox of original drawing; 0041; 94
- Aliberti, John Nicholas
  - [Untitled], 0042; 424; Pink eagle
- Alvarez Hallmark, Ilayali
  - [Untitled], paint on paper, collage; 0043; 295; Text: This is my country...
- Aljian, Stephen
  - [Untitled], 0044; 1590; "I am a middle age artist..."
- Aller, Renate
  - Afterwards, photograph; 0045; 1367; Photo of an older woman and a man looking out the window
- Altamura, Mauro
  - Nothing, digital image; 0046; 1386; Photo of the White House [i.e., U.S. Capitol] with text on bottom
- Altman, Josh
  - [Untitled], digital image; 0047; 797
- Alvarado, Lisa
  - Bringing the War Home/Its Just Another Day in America, 0048; 306; "Who is my enemy?"
- Alvarez, Desiree
  - Screaming Liberty, ink on paper; 0049; 1082; Image of the face of the Statue of Liberty screaming; in her open mouth is the NYC skyline
- Ambar, Anat
  - [Untitled], 0050; 1606
- Amezcua, Remy
  - 11.09.01, poem; 0050b; 3211; Palito...
- Amies-Bell, Linda
  - [Untitled], 0051; 736
- Amos-Murphy, Barb
  - [Untitled], comp art; 0051b; 3219; Cropt [sic] photos of World Trade buildings
- Anderegg, Elfi
  - December 2001, 0052; 533; Towers as grid
- Anderson, Chris
  - [Untitled], 0053; 531; "Dear Friends..."
- Anderson, Holly
  - [Untitled], 0054; 1507; Email posts
- Anderson, James
  - [Untitled], 0055; 138; Prose
- Anderson, James
  - [Untitled], 0056; 2271; Art is a difficult concept...
- Anderson, Larry
  - [Untitled], 0058; 1988; Missing tooth
- Anderson, Tom
  - [Untitled], 0059; 373
- Andreev, Michael Ricardo
  - Bird Cage, ink on paper; 0060; 1397; Black and white sillouette of a cage structure
- Andziewicz, Sandra
  - [Untitled], 0061; 441; Heart
- Ann, Beth
  - Eye Witness, digital print; 0063; 1979; W/face
- Annenberg, Marcia
  - Value Study, 0064; 407
- Annenberg, Morton
  - [Untitled], 0065; 403; Stabbed in the Back
- Annenberg, Morton
  - [Untitled], 0066; 404; You've got mail
- Annunziata, Frank
  - [Snapshot of New York City skyline with World Trade Center towers engulfed in smoke following the September 11th terrorist attack], Polaroid; 0066B; 3210
- Anonymous
  - [Untitled], 0071; 145; "Freedom" drawing from Mt. Ida College drawing class
- Anonymous
  - [Untitled], 0074; 625; "wish you were here..."
- Anonymous
  - [Untitled], 0075; 624; Wavy monster drawing
- Anonymous
  - One: Jesus, Mohammed, Buddha, digital image; 0076; 1090; The faces of Jesus, Mohammed, and Buddha digitally combined into one
- Anonymous
  - Viagra - Helping America Stand Firm, pencil on paper; 0077; 1066; Line drawing of an erect penis coming up from a flag pole, waving the American flag
- Anonymous
  - [Untitled], 0078; 1162; Online conversation and opinion
- Anonymous
  - [Untitled], digital image; 0080; 1415; Small photo of plane
- Anonymous
  - [Untitled], 0085; 1866; Heart w/peace
- Anonymous
  - [Untitled], 0086; 2295; God is love
- Anonymous
  - [Untitled], 0087; 2294; God is love
- Anonymous
  - [Untitled], 0088; 2293; I'm glad the Pakistani...
- Anonymous
  - [Untitled], 0089; 2292; God is love welfare of mankind
- Anonymous
  - Render to no one evil for evil, digital art; 0089b; 2279
- Anonymous
  - Rilke was Right - Aftermath, text; 0089c; 2276
- Antkowski, Maruen A.
  - [Untitled], poem; 0090; 31; Poem via email
- Arcieri, Ryan
  - [Untitled], comp art; 0090b; 3280
- Arena-Mastropaolo, Joan
  - Skyline Without Towers, 0091; 735
- Aretests, Etsetera
  - [Untitled], poem; 0093; 2286; I put my hand...
- Arias & Aragon
  - In Memoriam-Flower Towers, 0094; 1965
- Arroyo, Andrea
  - 9/11/01, New York City, drawing (digital print); 0095; 1826; Two towers with unreal in it
- Arthurs, Madeleine Hope
  - [Untitled], 0096; 123; Artwork
- Artoin
  - [Untitled], blurred photo; 0097; 2009
- Ashcraft, Hailey N.
  - [Untitled], typed text on paper; 0099; 756
- Auerbach, Marjorie
  - [Untitled], 0100; 307; "Torn From My City"
- Ausbury, Steve
  - [Untitled], photo w/writing; 0101; 1813
- Austen, Hartmut
  - [Untitled], artwork; 0102; 95; Via mail
- Austin, May
  - [Untitled], 0103; 857; Nowhere
- Avakian, Margo
  - [Untitled], 0104; 1201; Nagorno-Karabagh
- Aylon, Helene
  - All I Can Do Is Cover the Mirrors in the Ancient Tradition of Mourning, 0105; 1190; Burlap
- B., David
  - [Untitled], 0106; 1692; Home of the Brave
- B., Franke
  - [Untitled], 0107; 237; 1 of 2
- B., Franke
  - [Untitled], 0108; 238; 2 of 2
- Bacasa, Gerald J.
  - I (love) NY More Than You, 0109; 2196; I love NY more than you
- Bachhuber, Nina Lola
  - [Untitled], digital image; 0110; 1954; 4 photos and text "at once she sang..."
- Bachner, Barbara L.
  - Nothing is the Same, text and image; 0111; 1610; 3 paragraph essay over image of work
- Backstedt, Roseanne
  - [Untitled], print of a painting; 0112; 279; With "gone" in middle
- Badawi, Kim Tarek
  - Reactions Print, 0113; 2083; Image superimposed onto reactions notice
- Badawi, Kim Tarek
  - Found Object-My History, 0114; 2084; Fill in the blanks
- Badenhausen, LA Thoriel
  - Reaction, mixed media; 0115; 1363; Collage of a dark face with mouth open and teeth showing
- Bradford, Linda
  - Descent, drawing; 0116; 694; Dots
- Bagatta, Jason
  - [Untitled], 0117; 621; Drawing with people wearing houses on their heads
- Bailey, Christine
  - [Untitled], pencil and ballpoint pen on paper; 0118; 1484; Geometric line drawing with small slashes in horizontal rows across drawing
- Bajen-Gahm, Carol
  - [Untitled], acrylic gel medium & plaster, charcoal on cardboard; 0119; 1626; Image of person with head in their hands - face visible
- Bajpai, Raina
  - Postal Mailer, 0120; 1594; Return address Brad Steele
- Baker, Jonathan S.
  - Jenga, photograph; 0121; 944; Jenga photo
- Bakke, Erik
  - [Untitled], digital image; 0122; 1409; Canvas pattern with black line at bottom of horizontal page resembling the NYC skyline
- Balan, Ludger K.
  - Do You Trust Your Government?, computer print-out; 0123; 925; Do you trust your government?
- Baldridge, Jane
  - [Untitled], comp art; 0123b; 3282
- Ball, Lillian
  - On My Doorstep, photograph; 0124; 1101; Photograph of Marines walking down a city block
- Bang, Woo Song
  - [Untitled], digital image on paper; 0125; 772; An image of a white bible spread flat with curved test over it. Also included three gallery exhibition cards
- Bannon, Amy
  - [Untitled], 0126; 737
- Baptiste, Lennon Jno
  - [Untitled], 0127; 2077; Pliers
- Baptiste, Lennon Jno
  - [Untitled], 0128; 2078; Girl with Princess Lea hair
- Baptiste, Lennon Jno
  - [Untitled], 0129; 2079; Native American
- Baranik, Rudolph
  - Rudolph Baranik from Dictionary from the 24th century 1900, 0130; 1331; Given by May Stevens on behalf
- Barger, Robert
  - We are there, text; 0131; 3073
- Barnes, Remy
  - Embedded, photograph; 0132; 1482; Photo of a broken down car on a patch of grass
- Barnes, Remy
  - Many Rivers to Cross, 0133; 1481; Uneven horizontal lines across paper hpf. 2001
- Barnes, Tammy
  - [Untitled], 0134; 263; "Thank You We Will Never Forget" Tacoma
- Barnhart, Barbara
  - [Untitled], 0135; 724
- Barolini, Nicoletta
  - [Untitled], 0136; 1020; Image of a baby holding a globe in a woman's arms
- Barr, Susan
  - [Untitled], 0137; 1116; Question mark
- Barreto, Bernardo
  - [Untitled], digital image collage; 0138; 943; Eyes
- Barry, Judith
  - [Untitled], vellum; 0139; 1630; Fading faces - darker side is side to show. Color saturated sheet of vellum with faces
- Bartle, Richard
  - [Untitled], 0140; 2265; Image of NYC skyline behind cross-section of river w/shell oil drums
- Bassis, Aileen
  - [Untitled], 0141; 579; Phptp collage
- Bastidas, Hugo Xavier
  - Fire 1995, 0142; 1034
- Batty, Marilyn
  - Try harder to coexist, mixed media on paper; 0143; 421
- Batu, Suzan
  - [Untitled], ink on paper; 0144; 794
- Bauer, Ingrid
  - [Untitled], 0145; 485; FEMA employee card
- Baughn, Elaine Bentley
  - A Shining Gift, text on paper; 0146; 833; 4 stanza poem
- Bauman, Bruce
  - [Untitled], text on paper; 0147; 1577; "the skyline fractured..."
- Baumbauer, Dr. E.
  - [Untitled], digital photomontage; 0148; 3214; Terror must not prevail
- Baumbauer, Dr, Eberhard
  - [Untitled], color photo; 0148b; 3228
- Bayard
  - [Untitled], pencil on paper; 0149; 1632; One line drawn in the middle of the page
- Beallor, Fran
  - [Untitled], 0150; 754; NYC 2001 www.Franbeallor.com
- Bean, K.
  - [Untitled], 0151; 3325; Text on page "Go to Ground" top of page "Get Down" bottom of page
- Bear, Liza
  - M'Finda Kalunga Garden, photograph; 0152; 2194; Woman in garden
- Bear, Liza
  - New York City, Ground Zero, October 2001, photograph; 0153; 2195
- Bebout, Catherine
  - [Untitled], 0154; 910; Letter with stamps and letters
- Becht, Randi
  - [Untitled], embroidery on cotton cloth; 0155; 958
- Beck-Fink, Karen
  - Representative Body Bag, pastel; 0156; 1846
- Beckman, Ruth
  - [Untitled], mixed media; 0157; 2096; Drawing of three unicorns (1 of 2) (2096-2099)
- Beckman, Ruth
  - [Untitled], mixed media; 0158; 2097; Drawing of three unicorns (2 of 2) (2096-2099)
- Beckman, Ruth
  - [Untitled], mixed media; 0159; 2098; Drawing of figures (2096-2099)
- Beckman, Ruth
  - [Untitled], mixed media; 0160; 2099; Abstract flower image (2096-2099)
- Behr, Sheri Lynn
  - Once Upon a Time..., 0161; 455; Ghostly WTC buildings
- Behr-Johansen, Gerlinde
  - [Untitled], photograph; 0162; 691; Two light gray streaks
- Behr-Johansen, Gerlinde
  - [Untitled], photograph; 0162b; 690; Paint splatters w/red and black
- Beisher, Warren
  - [Untitled], collage; 0163; 1171; W/candles
- Beitz, Michael
  - [Untitled], 0164; 1356
- Belle, Erika
  - Broken Souls, charcoal, pencil and oil crayon on paper; 0165; 1012; Image of a radiating circle in upper lefthand corner with squares in the center
- Ferland, Ben
  - [Untitled], age: 13; 0167; 396
- Ben-Haim, Zigi
  - [Untitled], 0168; 659
- Ben-Shitrit, Orit
  - [Untitled], 0169; 683; Hands in many colors
- Benitez, Marimar
  - [Untitled], 0170; 2132; We are living in a historical...
- Bennett, Lisa
  - [Untitled], 0171; 490; "New York Times:..."
- Benson, Jane
  - She saw it with her own eyes but it looked like a movie..., 0172; 607
- Benson, Stefany
  - [Untitled], 0173; 745
- Bergery, Nicholas
  - [Untitled], digital image; 0175; 1375; Image of NYC skyline at night w/the face of a fireman in the sky
- Bergessen, Jim
  - Too Not True, 0176; 1794
- Bergmann, Meredith
  - September 11 (detail), 0177; 366
- Bergner, Babbs
  - Vest, 0178; 1483; A dark square printed against a light background in center of page
- Berkowitz, Michael J.
  - [Untitled], 0179; 224; "Amulet Costumes"
- Berkowitz, Terry
  - [Untitled], 0180; 1204; Amer. flag w/religious symbols
- Berman-Goldberg, Joanie
  - Fire-n-Ash 9/11, mixed media collage; 0181; 1434; Abstracted image of WTC disaster site
- Bernadini, Carlo
  - [Untitled], comp art; 0181b; 3286
- Berndhardt, Elise
  - [Untitled], 0182; 560; "To all staff if you want to volunteer..."
- Bernhard, Brian A.
  - [Untitled], 0183; 171; "and then it happened..." 1 of 2 (#167 companion piece)
- Bernhard, Brian A.
  - [Untitled], 0184; 167; "and then it happened ..." 2 of 2 (#171 companion piece)
- Berning, Mary E.
  - [Untitled], 0185; 1451
- Bertrand, Lucile
  - from the series, Portraits of Hair, 0186; 510
- Bertuzzi, Roger-Luis
  - [Untitled], 0187; 55; Quote from ecclesiastes
- Bever, Sandra
  - [Untitled], comp color print; 0187b; 3263
- Bilbao, Denise
  - ODE to NYC part two, cartoon; 0188; 427
- Biller, Andrea
  - [Untitled], 0189; 591; "Alert..."
- Billian, Cathey
  - [Untitled], 0190; 1112; Trees
- Binder, Lillian
  - [Untitled], 0191; 1853; Day so b
- Bingham, Bob
  - Searching for "Nanook of New York", ink, color photocopy on paper; 0192; 634; "Searching for Nanook..."
- Birgfeld, Fabian
  - [Untitled], 0193; 1249; The Thing
- Birgfeld, Fabian
  - [Untitled], 0194; 1250; Ashes
- Bishop, Johnny
  - [Untitled], 0195; 1689; Flag, sun and street
- Bisko, B.
  - [Untitled], digital image; 0196; 721; The words "Love Yourself" within image
- Bitterman and Duka
  - [Untitled], digital image; 0197; 820; WTC debris
- Bjorkenheim, Pam
  - Reactions, two sheets of mylar paper sewn together; 0197b; 1354
- Bjornsson, Ofeigur
  - Hlidskjalf, 0198; 1996; Throne of Odin
- BlackCyrus
  - [Untitled], 0199; 2006; We the people and magnifying glass
- Blagg, Max
  - Broken Windows, poem; 0200; 2266; Autumn coming in
- Blanchard, Marie
  - Can't stop watching tv, drawing (digital print); 0201; 1932
- Blick
  - [Untitled], email text; 0201b; 3240
- Blinder, Meryl
  - WTC III, drawing; 0202; 650; 3-D WTC repeated image
- Block, Bernard B.
  - [Untitled], text; 0202b; 3246
- Bloom, Stephanie
  - Lost Souls, 0203; 1619
- Blumberg, June
  - All Eyes on New York, pencil on paper; 0204; 1478; Line drawings of small spirals covering page
- Blumberg, June
  - [Untitled], pencil on paper; 0205; 1479; Line drawings of geometric spiral shapes
- Blurr, Buz
  - [Untitled], 0206; 76; Artwork via mail
- Bobb, Phyllis
  - Diary, September 14, 2001, 0207; 3286; Three people looking up with writing above
- Bodiu, Maria
  - [Untitled], 0208a; 206; Part of group from students of the Hudson School
- Bodiu, Maria
  - [Untitled], 0208b; 206; Part of group from students of the Hudson School
- Bona Pavelic, Mercy
  - [Untitled], 0209; 2; Submitted text via email
- Bonavoglia, Angela
  - Drawn to Wounded Ground, 0210; 286; Article from Chicago Tribune
- Boone, John
  - [Untitled], 0211; 77; Artwork via mail
- Boorujy, George
  - [Untitled], 0212; 977; "That's about as ridiculous as the Twin Towers falling down"
- Booth
  - [Untitled], 0213; 199; "born of simple cells..."
- Borger, Irene
  - [Untitled], black marker on yellow paper; 0214; 1864
- Boritz Berger, Sande
  - Charity, 0216; 2272; I had been mourning the death...
- Borowsky, Neal
  - [Untitled], artwork, drawing & text; 0217; 126
- Borum, Jenifer
  - Jenifer Borum, Journal 9/01, 0218; 1144; Journal entries
- Bottum, Win
  - [Untitled], 0219; 1565; Small sillouette of a figure freefalling down right side of page
- Boucourt, Eric
  - Mother and daughter passing Canal street, black and white photo; 0219b; 1350
- Bourbon, Matthew
  - Two Years, photocopy; 0220; 250; "my wife worked ..."
- Bourque, Loretta
  - [Untitled], 0221; 816
- Bowen, Carol
  - [Untitled], stencil/cutout; 0222; 217
- Bowen, Eddie
  - [Untitled], 0223; 2282; Massive money and the forces...
- Boyd, Eric
  - A Fine Line Separates Us From a Personal Madness, 0224; 3216
- Boyer, Brian
  - [Untitled], 0225; 3028; "ouch"
- Boyle, Christopher
  - [Untitled], 0227; 812; Drawing of a woman on the left side of page
- Boym, Constantin
  - Buildings of Disaster/ Souvenirs for the End of the Century, 0228; 1646; Image of World Trade Center, both towers with damage depicted, and Pentagon with partial collapse
- Brachman, Richard
  - [Untitled], painting; 0229; 635; airplanes
- Brody, Michele
  - [Untitled], paper; 0230; 1420; Text: "I was quite excited to find out"
- Bradford, Katherine
  - [Untitled], 0231; 1862; 2 women in birkas
- Bradley, Steve
  - I am speaking NOW, I will speak, 0232; 504; Lips
- Brady, Ryan
  - [Untitled], artwork; 0233; 81
- Brady & Sadri Gruche, Megan
  - [Untitled], artwork; 0234; 80
- Brafman, Marcy
  - [Untitled], 0236; 1921; Understand Jewish woe
- Brafman, Marcy
  - [Untitled], 0237; 1922; Corrugated landscape
- Brafman, Marcy
  - [Untitled], 0238; 1923; Twin airplanes
- Brahmst, Uli
  - DEHUMANISATION-2001, 0239; 978; Fleshy mound
- Bramblett, Frank
  - [Untitled], 0240; 911; Rubbed quarters
- Bramson, Phyllis
  - [Untitled], artwork; 0241; 70; Via mail
- Brandon, Lindsay
  - [Untitled], 0242; 3086; Mini Osama on a rocket
- Branscomb, Kristine
  - I wanted to know what 6,000 meant so I stuck 6,000 pins into cloth, cloth, foam, pins; 0243; 449; MFA Program
- Branscomb, Kristine
  - 6,000 Pins, cloth, foam, pins; 0244; 448; MFA Program
- Bravo, Tanya
  - [Untitled], 0245; 1175; Pics of missing people
- Brett, Nancy
  - 316 Second Graders Flowed North Escaping, 0246; 3072; Grey and gold painted image of a crowd of children
- Brew, Kathy
  - Center World Trade/Ode to Ground Zero, 0247; 2129
- Brickhouse, Farrell
  - Praise the Day, 0248; 1477; Calendar image with text to the right and bottom
- Bridgeman, Mary Churchill
  - [Untitled], 0249; 245; "my city with such a young history..." with photo
- Britton, Jay
  - [Untitled], 0250; 2119
- Brody, Jackie
  - [Untitled], text on paper; 0251; 741; A typed letter
- Brody, Michele
  - [Untitled], 0252; 1469; Students of P.S. 40 (#'s 1455-1469)
- Brody, Michele / David Wisnik
  - [Untitled], 0253; 1468; Students of P.S. 40 (#'s 1455-1469)
- Brody, Michele / Eva Busani
  - [Untitled], 0254; 1467; Students of P.S. 40 (#'s 1455-1469)
- Brody, Michele / Anne E. Malevanov
  - [Untitled], 0255; 1466; Students of P.S. 40 (#'s 1455-1469)
- Brody, Michele / Wilhem Jenik
  - [Untitled], 0256; 1465; Students of P.S. 40 (#'s 1455-1469)
- Brody, Michele
  - [Untitled], 0257; 1464; Students of P.S. 40 (#'s 1455-1469)
- Brody, Michele
  - [Untitled], 0258; 1463; Students of P.S. 40 (#'s 1455-1469)
- Brody, Michele
  - [Untitled], 0259; 1462; Students of P.S. 40 (#'s 1455-1469)
- Brody, Michele
  - [Untitled], 0260; 1461; Students of P.S. 40 (#'s 1455-1469)
- Brody, Michele
  - [Untitled], 0261; 1460; Students of P.S. 40 (#'s 1455-1469)
- Brody, Michele
  - [Untitled], 0262; 1459; Students of P.S. 40 (#'s 1455-1469)
- Brody, Michele
  - [Untitled], 0263; 1458; Students of P.S. 40 (#'s 1455-1469)
- Brody, Michele / Bert Sowa
  - [Untitled], 0264; 1457; Students of P.S. 40 (#'s 1455-1469)
- Brody, Michele
  - [Untitled], 0265; 1456; Students of P.S. 40 (#'s 1455-1469)
- Brody, Michele
  - [Untitled], 0266; 1455; Students of P.S. 40 (#'s 1455-1469)
- Brodyk, Andre
  - Exhumed, 0267; 3215; Blurry and yellow
- Brogan, Patricia Burke
  - Sept. 11, 2001, 0268; 196; Poem, "John Burke leans..."
- Brown, Lee Ann
  - Tilt Heaven, poem; 0270; 2076; Return to simple gifts
- Brown, Robert Delford
  - Funkupagan Manifesto, 0271; 277
- Bruce, Stewart
  - Candles in the wind ... tears in the eye..., 0272; 2283
- Brumer, Miriam
  - [Untitled], drawing; 0273; 197
- Buchanan, Christopher
  - [Untitled], poem; 0274; 2150; For me to claim...
- Buchanan, Craig N.
  - More Bang For Your Buck, collage; 0275; 997; Collage with a man with sunglasses in the middleground, and the text "Washington Update: Viral Threat" below him
- Buchanan, Keely Rose
  - [Untitled], collage; 0276; 996; Solid black background with the text: "Fear 1,063 images found", next to a patch of stars.
- Buchholz, Terry
  - Life on Moon, 0277; 1982; Gloved hand
- Bugk
  - [Untitled], 0278; 1599
- Bui, Phong
  - Nagz to the twins - Homage to the twins, 0279; 4
- Buntzen, Richard
  - [Untitled], 0280; 1763; Ivy
- Burkhart, Kathe